They paid. We did it.
Get back to the embassy.
They're going to fly us out of here.
You're starting to believe your role.
You're a recruit.
Not the one who gives orders.
What are you talking about?
It's over.
Not for us.
Listen.
If you do anything else.
they're going to storm the building.
Get ready.
Did they pay?
So?
Why should that stop us?
And this?
What about this? Huh?
I want them to pay in blood.
like the blood I saw spilled.
They smashed our country
then went back to their lives.
leaving us with the horror of war.
They must feel the same horror.
Maybe next time they will think twice
before they start a war and walk away.
- Where the fuck are you going?
- Look.
You pick your target.
and I will pick mine.
Guys. enough innocents have died.
The last blow should fall on the people
that caused the war.
I'm only going to spill the blood
of the guilty.
As justice for my family.
What about you?
Come on. bro.
More will die than in the first attack.
All of them will die.
We can get them outside.
The mayor is still here.
I was cheated out of killing him before.
- We get him first.
- Okay.
You distract his security team.